Lorraine Nue

事日名

le pages

From:

sharons300@hotmail.com <jobs@washingtonpost.com>

Sent:

Monday, July 20, 2015 9:46 PM

To:

Church Office

Subject:

Application submitted from Washington Post Jobs by Sharon Thomas for Buildings &

Ground Supervisor - Status: Emailed

Attachments:

sharon_Resume1.docx

The following application has been submitted from Washington Post Jobs

Candidate name: Sharon Thomas

Candidate email: sharons300@hotmail.com

Job title: Buildings & Ground Supervisor

Job link: https://jobs.washingtonpost.com/job/36010482/buildings-and-ground-supervisor/

Employer: St. Paul's Episcopal Church

Application date: 7/20/2015

Resume file: sharon_Resume1.docx

Other information:

Cover Letter: I would like to Thank you for your time

The Washington Post, 1150 15th St. NW, Washington, DC 20071

Sharon Thomas for Ref Use BLAKE

Summary of Qualifications

I have years of customer service experience and hands on experience as Ast Director of EVS / Operations Manger and Supervisor Experience In Building Maintenance and Janitorial. And also I have the ability to plan and prioritize and I always thank strategically and have the ability to handle multiple tasks and I always meet deadlines. I'm detailed oriented I lead but also listen to my Co workers in a positive light I find myself to be responsible and self motivated I'm a problem solver and a team player. I truly believe in what's best for the customer and The customer is important because without the customer there would be no business.

Education

1980 - 1984

McKinley High School

Washington DC

Professional Experience

07/12 – Present Carroll Manor Nursing Home Washington DC Responsible for selecting, training, supervising, and evaluating assigned staff of 20.

Position: Assistant Director Promoted 2/07/2014 Operations Manager Promoted 4/13/2013

Manage the Environmental Services Program within the facility to maintain the highest possible standards, I have a clear sense of urgency with customer and staff concerns.

I manage the hiring, evaluation, disciplining of EVS floor care and project staff, prepare work schedules and maintain adequate staffing levels.

Inspect cleanliness of the facility, sanitation and infection control; take corrective action where necessary.

Provide supportive leadership.

All departmental spaces to include housekeeping supply and administrative spaces are to be kept in accordance with the facility standards of cleanliness and appearance; all equipment clean, labeled and kept in good repair.

Develop a stable, competent work force and encourage personal growth of all personnel through periodic evaluation and review. Delivers strong operational performance by executing in accordance with Healthcare and regulatory agency standards and programs, continually monitoring operations and completing EVS quality assessments and necessary action plans to provide optimal environmental services.

Drive patient satisfaction and maintains client relationships through rounding.

Ensures compliance with appropriate infection prevention, safety, OSHA, Joint Commission and regulatory standards.

Assists in coordinating the activities of EVS staff to ensure efficient and cost effective utilization of staff, materials and equipment.

12/10-07/12 Providence Hospital Washington DC

Environmental Services Manager Environmental Services Supervisor Payroll

Payroll Using Krono's

Omni Buyer For Ordering Budget for supplies and equipment

Supervise staff of 33 Housekeepers in 1.2 Million Sq ft Building

3 Team leads

Dispatching work through phone, Cell Phone, Pager

Answering over 100 calls a day.

Handling Patient and Visitor Complaints.

Completing corrective Maintenance Work Orders to insure work has been complete.

Coordinates Before and After construction Cleanups

Ensure that all areas of Hospital are clean and free of Germs

Waste Management Recycling.

Arrange setup for events and break down events

Make sure these areas are cleaned daily.

All Public Areas, Patient Rooms, Admissions, IV Infusion, Oncology,

Main OR, Surgical, ER, Baby Nursery, In and out Surgery, Post

Anesthesia and Radiology

Discharge Cleaning 60 or more a day.

Attend Daily Management Meetings

Just a Few

I also assign staff daily and make sure setups and moves are done. Perform daily inspections walk grounds and help with cleaning areas when needed with Patient discharges. And Biohazard removal and Filing.

Laundry-Making sure that laundry and linen is processed and delivered in a timely manner.

Working with the supervisor with payroll and laundry procedures Ordering chemicals from Amato industries.

Ordering Linen

Making sure that machines are repaired.

Checking Machines and logs for lint removal

2003 - 2008 Washington Center On Aging Services DC Government Nursing Home

Environmental Services Supervisor

- Supervise over 50 Employees
- Supervise all activities of housekeeping staff and laundry and pest control.
- Preparation in annual operations and capital budgets.
- Estimating staffing and material requirements.
- Establishing and promulgate rules and regulations.
- Support the enforcement of Safety
- Oversee floor care projects.
- Maintaining the facility in a safe and sanitary state and in compliance with state and local and federal regulations.
- Inspect the facility daily to monitor all areas of environmental services.
- Coordinate the staff to maintain the exterior grounds.
- Support the DIR by identifying problem areas that need change.
- Interview hire, and discipline personnel in collaboration with the Director.
- Development of a quality assurance audit system.
- Assume responsibilities in this director's absence.
- Assist with the operations and new staff training.
- Assist in securing proposals sends bids for contracts as related to environmental services.
- Making sure equipment is kept in working order.

Arrange setups for events

2000-2003 Launch Coast Building Services College Park MD Operations Manager PEPCO CONTRACT

Meet with Customers.

Drive fleet of vehicles for maintenance jobs

- Organization Overview.
- Employee Orientations.
- Train Supervisors
- Employment Relations Employer Standards and guidelines.
- Payroll and Compensation and practices.
- Employee Benefits.
- Meet with customers
- Walk Pepco Plaints and buildings Over 600.000 sq ft.
- Employee health and safety.
- Employee Separation.

2000-2003 Melior Maids

RESIDENTIAL DEPARTMENT MANAGER

- Prepare work schedules.
- Making Sales Calls.
- · Preparing Payroll.
- Meeting with Potential Customers
- Providing Customer services.
- Maintaining company vehicles.
- Billing Customers and paying company bills.
- Train Employees in home cleaning.
- Training in proper usage of Chemicals

1999-2000 Launch Coast Services College Park MD Building Operations Manager

- Train 10 Supervisors.
- Budgeting Supplies.
- Budgeting Payroll Cost.
- Billing and Receiving.
- Meeting with Customers for problem solving.
- Inspecting Sites the largest being over 600,000 Sq Ft.

1996-1999 General Maintenance CO. Washington DC

Janitorial Cleaner

- Clean restrooms
- Vacuum offices
- Cleaning Offices
- Vacuuming Carpet
- Strip And Wax Floors
- Restock paper products
- Top scrub restroom floors

References

Calvin Sutton- Director of Environmental Services Washington Center

202-262-6998

Ayne Brown- Operations Director Carroll Manor- 703-994-6912

Dorothy Saunders - Manager Providence Hospital 202-489-5142 /202-269-7193

Melva Taylor- Ast Nursing Director 202-207-4090

Diane Frances- Ast Director Providence Hospital 202-269-7562

AWARDS Certificate's and Letters to include Annual Performance reviews To Show at Interview Many.